Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Political File, 1966-1980
  - Criswell, Mrs. Edna (Box 14)
  - Crofford, Mr. & Mrs. Verner R. (Box 14)
  - Cross, Mr. & Mrs. J. B. Jack (Box 14)
  - Crowe, Lloyd (Box 14)
  - Crawley, T. E. (Box 15)
  - Criminal Justice Council (Box 15)
  - Croucher, Mrs. Mary (Box 15)
  - Crowe, Sharon Lee (Box 15)
  - Crue, Mr. & Mrs. F. E. (Box 15)
  - Crutcher, Preston (Box 15)
  - Cuellar, Mrs. C. L. (Box 15)
  - Cuero, Texas (Box 15)
  - Cullers, Mr. Bill (Box 15)
  - Culpepper, Henry (Box 15)
  - Cultural Basins (Box 15)
  - Culver, Bob R. (Box 15)
  - Cummins, Charles K. (Box 15)
  - Cummings, J. P. (Box 15)
  - Cummings, Mr. & Mrs. James E. (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Jim (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Mr. & Mrs. Phillips (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Shem (Box 15)
  - Curran, Ms. Jerry (Box 15)
  - Currin, Fred (Box 15)
  - Currin, Jerry L. (Box 15)
  - Curry, Mr. Bill R. (Box 15)
  - Curry, Frances (Box 15)
  - Cypert, Roy W. (Box 15)
  - Czaya, Mr. & Mrs. John (Box 15)
  - Cox, Edley W. (Box 15)
  - Cox, Floyd (Box 15)
  - Cox, Mrs. James (Box 15)
  - Cox, Ms. Janet (Box 15)
  - Cox, Mr. John (Box 15)
  - Cox, William Floyd (Box 15)
  - Cox, William L. (Box 15)
  - Cozby, Ms. Geneva (Box 15)
  - Crabb, Ms. Elaine (Box 15)
  - Craddick, Rep. Tom (Box 15)
  - Craig, Mrs. Frank S. (Box 15)
  - Craig, Helen (Box 15)
  - Craig, Patricia (Box 15)
  - Craig, Ms. Vicki (Box 15)
  - Crain, Mrs. Aileen (Box 15)
  - Crain, Jack (Box 15)
  - Crain, John (Box 15)
  - Cramer, Bob (Box 15)
  - Crampton, Mrs. Barbara (Box 15)
  - Crampton, Ms. Barbara C. (Box 15)
  - Crane, R. C. (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Bo (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Mrs. C. W. (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Cheryl (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Earle (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Mary (Box 15)
  - Credit Bureau of Wichita Falls (Box 15)
  - Crelia, Mrs. Ray (Box 15)
  - Criminal Defense Lawyers Association (Box 15)
  - Criss, Rep. Lloyd (Box 15)
  - Criswell, Steven (Box 15)
  - Crittenden, Ms. Mary A. (Box 15)
  - Groan, Richard L. (Box 15)
  - Crocker, Mr. George (Box 15)
  - Cromwell, Terry (Box 15)
  - Crone, Ms. Virginia (Box 15)
  - Cross, Mrs. Lana (Box 15)
  - Cross, Mrs. Melton (Box 15)
  - Cross, Mrs. Robert K. (Box 15)
  - Crouch, Mrs. Heard (Box 15)
  - Croucher, Doc (Box 15)
  - Croucher, Merridel (Box 15)
  - Crow, Ms. Marjorie (Box 15)
  - Crowder, Ralph A. (Box 15)
  - Crowley, Mr. & Mrs. Joe (Box 15)
  - Cuelar, Ms. Jan (Box 15)
  - Crutchfield, Frank (Box 15)
  - Cruz, Lauro (Box 15)
  - Cubiane, Mrs. Mildred J. (Box 15)
  - Cubine, Mrs. Ronald E. (Box 15)
  - Culberson, Mrs. Alta (Box 15)
  - Culipher, Mrs. Roy (Box 15)
  - Cullers, William L. (Box 15)
  - Culley, Jerry (Box 15)
  - Cullin, Ruth (Box 15)
  - Cullum, James A. (Box 15)
  - Culwell, Pearl (Box 15)
  - Cummings, Mrs. Mary B. (Box 15)
  - Cummings, Mrs. Mary Ellen & Richard L. (Box 15)
  - Cummings, Russell (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Eddie (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Mr. & Mrs. George J. (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Ken (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, J. Phillips (Box 15)
  - Cupit, Mr. & Mrs. Jon (Box 15)
  - Cure (Box 15)
  - Curran, Edith (Box 15)
  - Curran, Mrs. Sally (Box 15)
  - Curtis, Ms. Ann C. (Box 15)
  - Cusuckeley, Clarence (Box 15)
  - Cutbirth, Mrs. Ann M. (Box 15)
  - Cutbirth, Mr. Dan (Box 15)
  - Campaign 1976 (Box 15)
  - Campaign 1973 (Box 15)
  - Campaign 1972 (Box 15)
  - Campaign Material (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Artie King (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Ms. Carol (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Ms. Debbie (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Miss Dorice (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Dovie (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Juanitta (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Ms. Sandra (Box 15)
  - Campbell, Mr. Voin (Box 15)
  - Camp Fire Girls (Box 15)
  - Camp, Mrs. Barbara (Box 15)
  - Campese, A. S. (Box 15)
  - Camps (Box 15)
  - Campsey, Harry (Box 15)
  - Canales, Terry A. (Box 15)
  - Cannedy, Ms. Mary (Box 15)
  - Cannedy, Mr. Ray (Box 15)
  - Cannon, Mr. & Mrs. T. H. (Box 15)
  - Cantrell, Grady (Box 15)
  - Cantrell, Jay (Box 15)
  - Canyon, Texas (Box 15)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 15)
  - Cappleman, Ed (Box 15)
  - Caraway, Bill (Box 15)
  - Carden, Jim (Box 15)
  - Cargill, Mr. & Mrs. Paul (Box 15)
  - Carlisle, Joyce (Box 15)
  - Carlisle, Mary (Box 15)
  - Carlson, Mrs. Dennis R. (Box 15)
  - Carmoney, Dr. Walter J. (Box 15)
  - Carney, Ruth (Box 15)
  - Carnwell, Lillian (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Mr. B. J. (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Dalton R. (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Donald W. (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Mrs. Helen (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Mike (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Mr. & Mrs. Robert (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Mrs. Rose M. (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Scott (Box 15)
  - Carr, Billie (Box 15)
  - Carr, Ms. Oueida M. (Box 15)
  - Carr, Waggoner (Box 15)
  - Carroll, Mr. William P. (Box 15)
  - Carrillo, O. P. (Box 15)
  - Carson, Archie Dale (Box 15)
  - Carswell, W. R. (Box 15)
  - Carter, Bob (Box 15)
  - Carter, Haydon Jr. (Box 15)
  - Carter, Jimmy (Box 15)
  - Cartwright, Rep. Donald (Box 15)
  - Cartwright, Mrs. M. L. (Box 15)
  - Carver, Dr. Richard C. (Box 15)
  - Cary, Reby (Box 15)
  - Cason, Ewell (Box 15)
  - Cason, Mrs. Rita (Box 15)
  - Casswell, Howard (Box 15)
  - Castillo, Freddie (Box 15)
  - Castle, Billy Ray (Box 15)
  - Cates, Phil (Box 15)
  - Cathy, Mr. Garland (Box 15)
  - Catron, John (Box 15)
  - Caudill, Rev. Ed (Box 15)
  - Causes (Box 15)
  - Cavenen, Ms. Charlie (Box 15)
  - Cavenius, Victor (Box 15)
  - Cayce, Vera (Box 15)
  - Censorship (Box 15)
  - Census (Box 15)
  - Center for Legislative Improvement (Box 15)
  - Center for Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 15)
  - Center for Urban Studies (Box 15)
  - Certainteed Corporation (Box 15)
  - Certified Public Accountants (Box 15)
  - Cerveny, Ms. Nancy (Box 15)
  - Ceverha, Rep. Bill (Box 15)
  - Ceta (Box 15)
  - Chadick, Justice T. C. (Box 15)
  - Chadwick, Jim (Box 15)
  - Chambers, David (Box 15)
  - Chambers, Mr. Gene (Box 15)
  - Chambers, H. Glenn (Box 15)
  - Chambliss, Ron (Box 15)
  - Chambus, Mrs. Wayne (Box 15)
  - Champ, Lamoin (Box 15)
  - Champion Spark Plug Company (Box 15)
  - Champman, Tom (Box 15)
  - Chancellor, Ms. Mary C. (Box 15)
  - Chancellor, Ms. Ruby (Box 15)
  - Chancellor, Virgil H. (Box 15)
  - Chandler, Mr. Don (Box 15)
  - Chandler, Mrs. Donald (Box 15)
  - Chandler, William & Norma (Box 15)
  - Chapman, Mr. Howard (Box 15)
  - Chapman, Tom (Box 15)
  - Chappell, Mrs. Lavon (Box 15)
  - Charity (Box 15)
  - Chastain, Mary (Box 15)
  - Chavez, Rep. Melchor (Box 15)
  - Cheatheam, Mrs. L. D. (Box 15)
  - Checks (Box 15)
  - Cheek, Mattie Lee (Box 15)
  - Chen, Fang (Box 15)
  - Chenault, Mrs. Jerry (Box 15)
  - Cherrington, Mike (Box 15)
  - Chesser, Tom (Box 15)
  - Chicanos (Box 15)
  - Chicosky, Mrs. Vicki (Box 15)
  - Child Abuse (Box 16)
  - Child Care - Aug. 21, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Child Care - May 1979 (Box 16)
  - Child Care 1979 (Box 16)
  - Child Care July 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Child Care June-May 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Child Care Jan. 1976-April 1977 (Box 16)
  - Child Care Jan. -April 1975 (Box 16)
  - Child Care April-Dec. 1975 (Box 16)
  - Culp, A. R. (Box 17)
  - Cummings, Mr. C. H. (Box 17)
  - Cummings, J. P. (Box 17)
  - Cummings, Russell (Box 17)
  - Cummings, Chas. K. (Box 17)
  - Cunningham, Mr. B. J. (Box 17)
  - Cunningham, Kenneth (Box 17)
  - Cunningham School (Box 17)
  - Cupp, Mrs. Norvil R. (Box 17)
  - Curry, Mrs. Les (Box 17)
  - Curry, Mr. Phil (Box 17)
  - Curtis, Mr. Leon (Box 17)
  - Cutbirth, Mr. & Mrs. R. W. (Box 17)
  - Crusenberry, Mrs. Robert C. (Box 17)
  - Cable Television (Box 17)
  - Caby, Mrs. Laton P. (Box 17)
  - Cackett, Mr. Grover E. (Box 17)
  - Cackler, Mrs. Cyde (Box 17)
  - Cahoon, Mr. & Mrs. Frank Kell (Box 17)
  - Cain, Pat (Box 17)
  - Cain, Mr. Ray L. (Box 17)
  - Caldwell, C. S. (Chuck) (Box 17)
  - Caldwell, La Verne (Box 17)
  - Callinhan, Mr. A. A. (Box 17)
  - Cameron, Archie (Box 17)
  - Camp, Miss Berniece W. (Box 17)
  - Camp, Mrs. Gene (Box 17)
  - Campbell, Don (Box 17)
  - Campbell, Mrs. H. M. (Box 17)
  - Campese, A. S. (Box 17)
  - Can Gobbler (Box 17)
  - Canadian, Texas (Box 17)
  - Cannedy, Mrs. Christine (Box 17)
  - Cannon, Mrs. Etta M. (Box 17)
  - Cantrell, Grady (Box 17)
  - Capitol Guide Service (Box 17)
  - Capitol Parking Committee (Box 17)
  - Capitol Station (Box 17)
  - Capitol Tax Letter (Box 17)
  - Capron, C. L. (Box 17)
  - Cards (Box 17)
  - Cargill, Robert (Box 17)
  - Carillo, Mr. & Mrs. Oscar (Box 17)
  - Carlson, Lowell (Box 17)
  - Carnahan, Donald Robert (Box 17)
  - Carnation Company (Box 17)
  - Carnes, Bill (Box 17)
  - Carpenters Union (Box 17)
  - Carr, Mrs. Carlton (Box 17)
  - Carr, Waggoner (Box 17)
  - Carroll, Mrs. Helen (Box 17)
  - Carson, Dan (Box 17)
  - Carter, Bob R. (Box 17)
  - Carter, Miss Claudia (Box 17)
  - Carter, Guy (Box 17)
  - Carter, Dr. I. A. (Box 17)
  - Carter, J. R. (Box 17)
  - Carter, Mrs. Ken (Box 17)
  - Cartwright, Anson H. (Box 17)
  - Carver, Mrs. A. B. (Box 17)
  - Carver, Dr. Richard C. (Box 17)
  - Casey, Bob (Box 17)
  - Cash, Mack (Box 17)
  - Cason, Dr. Larry (Box 17)
  - Castillo, David (Box 17)
  - Castillo, Freddie (Box 17)
  - Castledine, Mr. & Mrs. Jimmy (Box 17)
  - Catholic Church (Box 17)
  - Catholic Daughters of America (Box 17)
  - Cato, Mrs. Cora (Box 17)
  - Catron, Mrs. Mary E. (Box 17)
  - Cattle (Box 17)
  - Caubie, J. V. (Box 17)
  - Caven, Mr. & Mrs. Walter (Box 17)
  - Cavin, Alton H. (Box 17)
  - Cavness, Charles H. (Box 17)
  - Cavness, Don (Box 17)
  - Cemeteries (Box 17)
  - Central Christian Church of Austin (Box 17)
  - Cemetery Trust Fund (Box 17)
  - Central Texas College (Box 17)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 17)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (Box 17)
  - Chambers, R. E. Gene (Box 17)
  - Chamless, Joe (Box 17)
  - Champ, Lemoin (Box 17)
  - Charlesworth, William E. (Box 17)
  - Chatterton, Mrs. Edgar G. (Box 17)
  - Cheek, Mrs. Harley (Box 17)
  - Chemicals (Box 17)
  - Cherry, Mr. Robert G. (Box 17)
  - Cheshire, Dr. & Mrs. McKinley Jr. (Box 17)
  - Chester, Mrs. Glenn (Box 17)
  - Chester, Ms. Lottie Marie (Box 17)
  - Child Custody (Box 17)
  - Childers, Clyde J. (Box 17)
  - Childers, Tommy G. (Box 17)
  - Children's Center (Box 17)
  - Children of the Confederacy (Box 17)
  - Childress, Miss Frances (Box 17)
  - Childress, Roy (Box 17)
  - Chiropractors (Box 17)
  - Chisholm Trail Centennial Commission (Box 17)
  - Criminal Justice Council (Box 17)
  - Christenberry, Miss Agnes (Box 17)
  - Christenson, Miss Elizabeth (Box 17)
  - Christian, Mr. George (Box 17)
  - Christian Science (Box 17)
  - Christian, Mr. & Mrs. Tom (Box 17)
  - Christie, C. B. Jr. (Box 17)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 17)
  - Christopher, Lois B. O.D. (Box 17)
  - Church of The Living God P. G. of T. (Box 17)
  - Cabaniss, Blanchie R. (Box 17)
  - Cabaniss, J. C. (Box 17)
  - Caceres, Carlos (Box 17)
  - Caddell, Dorothy (Box 17)
  - Caffee - Bellamy & Assoc. (Box 17)
  - Caldcleugh, Mr. & Mrs. Bill A. (Box 17)
  - Caldcleaugh, Pat (Box 17)
  - Caldwell, Dorothy E. (Box 17)
  - Caldwell, Neil (Box 17)
  - Calendar (Box 17)
  - Caley, Annette L. (Box 17)
  - Caley, Mr. & Mrs. Lawton P. (Box 17)
  - Calhoun, Frank W. (Box 17)
  - Callaway, Martha (Box 17)
  - Callon, Jack S. (Box 17)
  - Calvert, Robert S. (Box 17)
  - Calvert, Robert W. (Box 17)
  - Calvillo, Ms. Eleanor (Box 17)
  - Calvit, Joe (Box 17)
  - Cameron, Mrs. W. A. (Box 17)
  - Camp Fire Girls (Box 17)
  - Campaign 1974 - File 1 (Box 17)
  - Campaign 1974 - File 2 (Box 17)
  - Campaign 1973 (Box 17)
  - Campaign 1972 - File 2 (Box 17)
  - Campaign 1972 - File 1 (Box 17)
  - Campaign 1966 (Box 17)
  - Child Care, Inc. (Box 18)
  - Child Welfare (Box 18)
  - Childers, Marilyn (Box 18)
  - Childress, Marilyn (Box 18)
  - China (Box 18)
  - Choate, Gladys (Box 18)
  - Chrietzbert, Dr. C. (Box 18)
  - Christian Life Commission (Box 18)
  - Christie, Joe (Box 18)
  - Chriswell, Stephen (Box 18)
  - Chupik, Mr. & Mrs. Arthur W. (Box 18)
  - Church of Scientology of Texas (Box 18)
  - Church Women United in Texas (Box 18)
  - Churchill, Peter J. (Box 18)
  - CIBA-GEIGY (Box 18)
  - Cities (Box 18)
  - Citizen Band Radio (Box 18)
  - Citizens Conference on State Legislatures (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Human Development (Box 18)
  - Citizens Legislative Oversight Group (Box 18)
  - Citizens United for Rehabilitation of Errants (CURE) (Box 18)
  - City Government (Box 18)
  - City National Bank (Box 18)
  - City View Junior High (Box 18)
  - City View School (Box 18)
  - City of Wichita Falls (Box 18)
  - Civil Liberties Union (Box 18)
  - Civiletto, Ms. Elvira (Box 18)
  - Civil Rights (Box 18)
  - Clack, Mr. & Mrs. Charles (Box 18)
  - Clack, Mrs. E. E. (Box 18)
  - Clear, Mary (Box 18)
  - Clanton, Mr. & Mrs. Lewis (Box 18)
  - Clapp, Ken (Box 18)
  - Clark, Bill (Box 18)
  - Clark, Dennis (Box 18)
  - Clark, Dr. & Mrs. Gordon G. (Box 18)
  - Clark, Mr. & Mrs. Henry M. (Box 18)
  - Clark, J. H. (Box 18)
  - Clark, Jim (Box 18)
  - Clark, Mike (Box 18)
  - Clark, Mildred Mignon (Box 18)
  - Clark, R. Lee (Box 18)
  - Clark, Hon. Ramsey (Box 18)
  - Clark, Mrs. Tom (Box 18)
  - Clark, V. P. (Box 18)
  - Clarkson, Garland (Box 18)
  - Classroom Teachers Association (Box 18)
  - Clay County (Box 18)
  - Clayton, Bill (Box 18)
  - Clear Lake City (Box 18)
  - C.L.E.A.T. (Box 18)
  - Cleaver, Mr. G. J. (Box 18)
  - Clements, Bill (Box 18)
  - Clements, Mr. Roger (Box 18)
  - Clemmer, Ms. Lila (Box 18)
  - Cleveland, Shenista (Box 18)
  - Clifford, Ms. JoAnne (Box 18)
  - Clingman, Jess (Box 18)
  - Clipson, Mr. Tim (Box 18)
  - Close, Rep. Bob (Box 18)
  - Clower, Mrs. J. C. (Box 18)
  - Clower, Ron (Box 18)
  - Clymer, Ray Jr. (Box 18)
  - Coal (Box 18)
  - Coal Slurry (Box 18)
  - Costal Zone (Box 18)
  - Coats, Nealie (Box 18)
  - Coats, Mr. Sam (Box 18)
  - Cobb, Mr. & Mrs. Jasper (Box 18)
  - Cobble, Allen (Box 18)
  - Coburn, Robert W. (Box 18)
  - Coca-Cola (Box 18)
  - Cochran, Mr. & Mrs. Jim (Box 18)
  - Cockrell, Mr. & Mrs. Calvin (Box 18)
  - Coen, Mrs. C. W. (Box 18)
  - Coetter, Kenneth (Box 18)
  - Cofer, Rep. Lanell (Box 18)
  - Coffee, Guy (Box 18)
  - Coffman, Vaughn (Box 18)
  - Cohn, Mr. David (Box 18)
  - Coker, F. M. (Box 18)
  - Colclasure, Ray (Box 18)
  - Cole, CM Sgt. & Mrs. C. J. (Box 18)
  - Cole, James D. (Box 18)
  - Coleman, Dan (Box 18)
  - Coleman, Don (Box 18)
  - Coleman, La Verne (Box 18)
  - Coleman, Linda J. (Box 18)
  - Coleman, Mrs. Mike (Box 18)
  - Coleman, Rep. Donald D. (Box 18)
  - Coleman, Rep. Tom (Box 18)
  - Colhouer, Ms. Karen K. (Box 18)
  - Collazo, Frank Jr. (Box 18)
  - College Republicans (Box 18)
  - Collett, John (Box 18)
  - Colley, Mrs. Milton (Box 18)
  - Collier, Ms. Barbara J. (Box 18)
  - Collier, Eula L. (Box 18)
  - Collins, Mr. & Mrs. Ben (Box 18)
  - Collins, Mr. & Mrs. Floyd (Box 18)
  - Collins, Mr. & Mrs. Grant (Box 18)
  - Collins, Dr. James W. (Box 18)
  - Collins, Mr. & Mrs. Jim (Box 18)
  - Collins, Ms. La Vada (Box 18)
  - Collins, Tommy (Box 18)
  - Combined Law Enforcement Association of Texas (Box 18)
  - Commission for the Blind (Box 18)
  - Commission for the Deaf (Box 18)
  - Commission on Inter-governmental Relations (Box 18)
  - Committee on Political Education (Box 18)
  - Commission on Alcoholism (Box 18)
  - Commission on the Arts & the Humanities (Box 18)
  - Common Cause (Box 18)
  - Communication Workers of America (Box 18)
  - Community Action Corporation (Box 18)
  - Community Colleges (Box 18)
  - Community Council (Box 18)
  - Community Education Program (Box 18)
  - Community Property (Box 18)
  - Comptroller of Public Accounts (Box 18)
  - Concern (Box 18)
  - Confederate Air Force (Box 18)
  - Conference of Churches (Box 18)
  - Conference of Urban Counties (Box 18)
  - Congress (Box 18)
  - Conley, Jack (Box 18)
  - Conn, Mrs. Aurelia E. (Box 18)
  - Connally, John (Box 18)
  - Conner, Dr. James (Box 18)
  - Conroy, Mr. & Mrs. R. A. (Box 18)
  - Conservation (Box 18)
  - Conservative Caucus (Box 18)
  - Constables (Box 18)
  - Constitutional Amendments (Box 18)
  - Constitutional Convention (Box 18)
  - Constitutional Revision #4 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision #3 - 1974 File 1 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision #3 - 1974 File 2 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision March-April 1974 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision February 1974 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision January 1974 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision Sept. - Dec. 1973 (Box 19)
  - Constitutional Revision 1971- Aug. 1973 (Box 19)
  - Consumers (Box 19)
  - Consumer Affairs (Box 19)
  - Consumer Credit (Box 19)
  - Consumer Credit Commission (Box 19)
  - Consumer Protection (Box 19)
  - Continental Telephone of Texas (Box 19)
  - Continental Trailways (Box 19)
  - Contingent Expense 1980 (Box 20)
  - Contingent Expense 1979 (Box 20)
  - Contingent Expense 1977 (Box 20)
  - Contingent Expense 1976 (Box 20)
  - Contingent Expense 1975 (Box 20)
  - Contingent Expense 1971 (Box 20)
  - Converse, Mr. & Mrs. Clayton P. (Box 20)
  - Coody, Bill (Box 20)
  - Cook, Dr. & Mrs. Charles Eckman (Box 20)
  - Cook, Mrs. Gary D. (Box 20)
  - Cook, Gertrude (Box 20)
  - Cook, Dr. Hulen J. Jr. (Box 20)
  - Cook, James E. (Box 20)
  - Cook, Mr. & Mrs. Joe P. (Box 20)
  - Cook, Melissa (Box 20)
  - Cooley, Ms. Kay (Box 20)
  - Coombs, Harvey L. (Box 20)
  - Cooper, Glen W. (Box 20)
  - Cooper, Terry (Box 20)
  - Cooper, W. R. (Bill) (Box 20)
  - Cooperman, Jackie (Box 20)
  - Coordinating Board (Box 20)
  - Cope, Mrs. Odys O. (Box 20)
  - Copelin, Carroll (Box 20)
  - Copelin, Mr. & Mrs. Dewey (Box 20)
  - Coppage, John (Box 20)
  - Corbett, Harold (Box 20)
  - Corn, Mrs. D. W. (Box 20)
  - Cornelius, Barbara (Box 20)
  - Cornelius, T. M. (Box 20)
  - Corps of Engineers (Box 20)
  - Corpus Christi (Box 20)
  - Corrections (Box 20)
  - Correll, David (Box 20)
  - Cory, Dick (Box 20)
  - Cosmetologist (Box 20)
  - Cost, Terry (Box 20)
  - Costello, A. T. (Al) (Box 20)
  - Cottle, Mr. & Mrs. George C. (Box 20)
  - Cotton, Steve (Box 20)
  - Cottrell, Rev. William L. Jr. (Box 20)
  - Councils of Government (Box 20)
  - Coulson, Mrs. Iola (Box 20)
  - Council of State Governments (Box 20)
  - Counseling (Box 20)
  - Counties (Box 20)
  - County Clerks (Box 20)
  - County Court at Law (Box 20)
  - County Employoees (Box 20)
  - County Government (Box 20)
  - County Judges & Commissioners Association of Texas (Box 20)
  - County Judges (Box 20)
  - Court Procedures (Box 20)
  - Court Reporters (Box 20)
  - Courts (Box 20)
  - Covey, E. L. (Box 20)
  - Covey, Mrs. Floyd (Box 20)
  - Coward, Mr. & Mrs. Wayne (Box 20)
  - Cowardin, Mr. & Mrs. Raymond (Box 20)
  - Cowart, Mrs. Earl (Box 20)
  - Cowart, Ms. Gwen (Box 20)
  - Allred, David (Box 20)
  - Dabbs, Mrs. Otiol (Box 20)
  - Dailey, Karen (Box 20)
  - Doughty, Ruby (Box 20)
  - Douglas, Mrs. Emma (Box 20)
  - Douglas, Juanita (Box 20)
  - Douglas, Judge Leon (Box 20)
  - Douglas, William O. (Box 20)
  - Doyle, Mrs. Nelle M. (Box 20)
  - Driscoll, Mrs. Greta (Box 20)
  - Dryden, Dr. Charles (Box 20)
  - Duffield, Robert (Box 20)
  - Duggan, Lee Jr. (Box 20)
  - Dugger, Ronnie (Box 20)
  - Duncan, Miss Delores (Box 20)
  - Duncan, Ethel (Box 20)
  - Duncan, Mrs. Kennon (Box 20)
  - Duncan, Norman (Box 20)
  - Dunlop, Hank (Box 20)
  - Dunn, Martha (Box 20)
  - Durgan, Claude (Box 20)
  - Dwyer, Mr. & Mrs. George N. (Box 20)
  - Eblen, Mrs. Nell (Box 20)
  - Elliott, Mr. & Mrs. Johnts (Box 20)
  - Elliott, S. M. (Box 20)
  - Flowers, Mrs. Vera (Box 20)
  - England, Mr. & Mrs. Grady (Box 20)
  - England, R. S. (Box 20)
  - English, Mr. J. R. (Box 20)
  - English, Larry (Box 20)
  - English, Lloyd L. (Box 20)
  - Engstrom, Mrs. Mary M. (Box 20)
  - Enloe, Mrs. Charles H. (Box 20)
  - Erdmann, Henry E. (Box 20)
  - Erskine, Mrs. Elvine E. (Box 20)
  - Erwin, C. C. (Box 20)
  - Escue, Herman (Box 20)
  - Esparza, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph Jr. (Box 20)
  - Estes, Ruth (Box 20)
  - Estill, Mr. J. F. Jr. (Box 20)
  - Eubank, Garland (Box 20)
  - Eustace, Mr. Alvis (Box 20)
  - Eustiee, Miss I. J. (Pinky) (Box 20)
  - Evans, Mr. Cleddie (Box 20)
  - Evans, Miss Janine (Box 20)
  - Evans, Mrs. Louise (Box 20)
  - Evans, Milton C. (Box 20)
  - Evans, Roger (Box 20)
  - Evans, Vernon Q. (Box 20)
  - Evans, Vickie Anna (Box 20)
  - Evans, Vinnie (Box 20)
  - Evans, Virgil (Box 20)
  - Evans, Mrs. Virginia (Box 20)
  - Evans, Wayland (Box 20)
  - Evans, William J. (Box 20)
  - Ewing, Victor R. (Box 20)
  - Eyssen, Tim (Box 20)
  - Ezell, F. Kelley (Box 20)
  - Davis, Gerald (Box 20)
  - Deaton, Mr. & Mrs. Cliff (Box 20)
  - Deffenbaugh, C. H. (Box 20)
  - Del Toro, Sgt. & Mrs. I. S. (Box 20)
  - "Dere Diry" Part 1 - David Allred (June 30, 1951 - Aug. 13, 1954 Diary) (Box 20)
  - "Dere Diry" Part II - David Allred (Aug.14, 1954 - Sept.1, 1954 Diary) (Box 20)
  - "Dere Diry" Part III - David Allred (Sept. 6, 1954 - June 14, 1955 Diary) (Box 20)
  - DeSamper, Hugh (Box 20)
  - Dickey, Mr. & Mrs. Richard (Box 20)
  - Dryden, Mrs. Sallie A. (Box 20)
  - Duffey, Miss Susan Randolph (Box 20)
  - Duffey, Rev. & Mrs. Paul A. (Box 20)
  - Dirty Thirty - File 1 (Box 21)
  - Dirty Thirty - File 2 (Box 21)
  - Discover Texas Association (Box 21)
  - Distributive Education (Box 21)
  - District Clerks (Box 21)
  - District & County Attorneys Association (Box 21)
  - Divorce Laws (Box 21)
  - Dixon, Carl (Box 21)
  - Dixon, Floyd E. (Box 21)
  - Dixon, Glenn W. (Box 21)
  - Dixon, Mr. Jesse G. (Box 21)
  - Dixon, Raymond B. (Box 21)
  - Dobbins, Dr. T. M. (Box 21)
  - Dobson, Sam (Box 21)
  - Dockery, John David (Box 21)
  - Doctors (Box 21)
  - Dodson, Mrs. D. C. (Box 21)
  - Doggett, Lloyd (Box 21)
  - Doing, Mr. & Mrs. Larry (Box 21)
  - Dolan, Miss Connie (Box 21)
  - Dollar, Billy R. (Box 21)
  - Dollar, Mrs. Carol (Box 21)
  - Donaldson, Jerry (Box 21)
  - Donnell, Barry (Box 21)
  - Donnell, Kenneth (Box 21)
  - Donnell, Mrs. Rosa (Box 21)
  - Donnell, R. Shirley (Box 21)
  - Donnell, Mr. & Mrs. William L. (Box 21)
  - Donovan, Bill (Box 21)
  - Donovan, Mr. & Mrs. Terrence J. (Box 21)
  - The Donutty Shop (Box 21)
  - Doten, Ms. June (Box 21)
  - Dotter, Gary R. (Box 21)
  - Doran, Hilary B. (Box 21)
  - Dorbandt, Dr. Barton W. (Box 21)
  - Doty, William R. (Author: Signed Book Inside) *for Discoverability purposes (Box 21)
  - Douglass, M. E. Jr. (Box 21)
  - Douglass, Mr. Melvyn Lee (Box 21)
  - Dougherty, James (Box 21)
  - Doughty, Auda (Box 21)
  - Douglas, Mr. & Mrs. Alan (Box 21)
  - Douthitt, Frank J. (Box 21)
  - Dow Chemical U. S. A. (Box 21)
  - Dowdy, Mrs. Albert (Box 21)
  - Dowdy, G. S. (Box 21)
  - Dowlearn, Leonard P. (Box 21)
  - Downing, Mrs. Kay (Box 21)
  - Downing, Mr. Layton (Box 21)
  - Downing, Miss Mary (Box 21)
  - Downtain, Dr. C. G. (Box 21)
  - Downtown Merchants Assoc. (Box 21)
  - Doyle, Mr. & Mrs. Terry (Box 21)
  - Dragoo, Mrs. Edna (Box 21)
  - Dramberger, A. L. "Tony" (Box 21)
  - Draughons Business College (Box 21)
  - Dray, Clifford (Box 21)
  - Dredging (Box 21)
  - Dressler, Amy (Box 21)
  - Dressler, Nancy (Box 21)
  - Driver, Judge & Mrs. Temple (Box 21)
  - Driver's Education (Box 21)
  - Drivers Licenses (Box 21)
  - Driver Safety (Box 21)
  - Driver Training (Box 21)
  - Druce, Carole (Box 21)
  - Drugs (Box 21)
  - Drummond, H. W. (Box 21)
  - Douglas, Mr. & Mrs. A. R. (Box 21)
  - Downtown Baptist Church (Box 21)
  - Dryden, Dr. Charles B. Jr. (Box 21)
  - Dubberley, Mrs. Madie (Box 21)
  - Dublin, Kathryn Reed (Box 21)
  - DuBose, Gene (Box 21)
  - Duce, Miss Elna Mae (Box 21)
  - Duck, Ray Lynn (Box 21)
  - Dudley, Mr. Elvin (Box 21)
  - Dudley, Mr. Harold K. (Box 21)
  - Dudley, Jack (Box 21)
  - Dudley, H. B. (Box 21)
  - Duffle, Shirley (Box 21)
  - Duggan, Brad (Box 21)
  - Duggan, Brenda (Box 21)
  - Duggan, Mrs. Jane (Box 21)
  - Dugger, Mr. Roy W. (Box 21)
  - Duke University (Box 21)
  - Duke, William S. (Box 21)
  - Duncan, Bobbie (Box 21)
  - Duncan, Mr. George W. (Box 21)